# SAYED **MURADI**

233 West Grant Line Rd Apt#125

Tracy, CA 95376 🔒

(209)637-1136

Asem.afg997@gmail.com 

✓



#### **OBJECTIVE**

Dynamic and motivated professional with vast IT experience. Skills that others coworker have complimented me on throughout my career include computer networking, analytical thinking and creative problem solving. Ability to apply customer service concepts to IT to improve user experience for clients, employees and customers.



#### **EDUCATION**

### High School Diploma | Zohor-E-Wahdat High School

2012-2015

I Finished High school in Afghanistan

#### IT Certificate | San Joaquin Delta College

2018-PRESENT

Currently I'm attending classes at San Joaquin Delta College with a focus in computer science.



#### EXPERIENCE

#### Computer Technician | Asian Market, Kabul Afghanistan

2011 - 2015

Basic duties included: including but not limited to, repairing and servicing computers of both PC and MAC. Removed viruses, data, backups, hardware repair, software installation and upgrades. Troubleshooted computers and gave diagnosis with performing final repair.

#### Phone Technician | Game plus

2017 - 2018

My basic duties included: I fixed peripheral problems with camera, battery, charging port, screens, and other issues, on Samsung, iPhone and iPad also.

### Computer and Phone Technician | Manteca Computer Services and cell phone Repair

2018 - 2019

Basic duties during this year was: fixing and communicating with customers about issues

IPhone: battery, charging port, screen, camera, water damage, boot loop, speaker, iTunes and etc.

IPad: screen, battery, home button, charging port, camera, speaker, iTunes, and etc.

Computer: diagnosing the issues, virus removal, over heat issue, screen replacement, battery, hinge fixing and cosmetic problems, soldering, OS corruption, email issues, slow startup problems, date backup and installing all type of OS system.

## Cell Phone and Computer Technician | Brentwood Game Exchange and Cell Phone Repair

2019-PRESENT

My basic duties are: fixing all type phone, computers, iPad, gaming consoles,



#### **SKILLS**

- Networking, LAN, WAN, WINS, DNS, DHCP, POP3, SMTP, FTP, VPN, Ethernet
- Computer Systems, windows 2000/XP/Vista/7/8/10

- Hardware: Cisco Series Routers,
   Netgear Routers, 3com, Hubs, Dell
   Workstations, Mac workstation, PBX
   systems, Cloud Servers, Asus
   motherboards, HP motherboards, Dell
   Motherboards, Gaming laptop and
   desktop motherboard.
- Strengths: computer hardware repair, fixing computers and phones after drops, water damage, and other catastrophic damage, fixing phone screens, batteries, camera, troubleshooting customer technical issues in a timely manner.